Guide to the Campus Council records, 1998-2012 UA.31.02.0005
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Campus Council records
1998-2012
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Campus Council.
UA.31.02.0005
3.5 Linear Feet
The Duke University Campus Council is dedicated to providing support and direction for students through active leadership in the community and is the primary governing body of residential life issues. Collection contains organizational materials relating to the daily operations of the Campus Council.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Historical Note
As representatives of the residential student body, the Duke University Campus Council is dedicated to providing support and direction for students through active leadership in the community. As the primary governing body of residential life issues, they strive to enhance campus life by implementing fair and thoughtful policies, in addition to providing quality programming throughout the year. As the umbrella organization for House, Quad, East Campus and Central Campus Councils, it is their goal to make living on campus a safe, educational, and enjoyable experience for all.
Collection Overview
Collection contains organizational materials relating to the daily operations of the Campus Council including agendas and minutes for the general Council and executive board; newspaper articles, communications, a residential governance leadership manual, photographs and scrapbooks. Also included are captures of the Campus Council website from 2010-2012.
Duke University. Campus Council.; Duke University -- Students
- Campus Council, 1998-1999; 4 folders (Box 1)
- Campus Council, agendas and minutes, 1998-1999; 3 folders (Box 1)
- Campus Council, executive board, 1998-1999; 3 folders (Box 1)
- Newspaper articles for Campus Council, 1998-1999 (Box 1)
- Campus Social Board, 1999 (Box 1)
- Rough report, survey drafts, residential life papers, 1999; 2 folders (Box 1)
- Campus Council, 1999-2000; 4 folders (Box 1)
- Campus Council, agendas, minutes, and requests for funds, 1999-2000; 1-5 of 8 folders (Box 1)
- Campus Council, agendas, minutes, and requests for funds, 1999-2000; 6-8 of 8 folders (Box 2)
- Campus Council, executive board, 1999-2000; 4 folders (Box 2)
- Newspaper articles for Campus Council, 1999-2000 (Box 2)
- Campus Council retreat, photo scrapbook, circa 2000 (Box 2)
- Devil's Eve, photos, 2000 (Box 2)
- Campus Council, 2000-2001; 3 folders (Box 2)
- Campus Council, agendas and minutes, 2000-2001; 3 folders (Box 2)
- Campus Council, executive board, 2000-2001; 3 folders (Box 2)
- Campus Council, requests for funds, 2000-2001; 5 folders (Box 2)
- Housing statistics, Autumn 2001 (Box 2)
- Campus Council, requests for funds, 2001-2002; 3 folders (Box 3)
- Newspaper articles for housing and Campus Council, 2001-2002 (Box 3)
- Lil Sibs Weekend, 2002 (Box 3)
- Campus Council, 2002-2003; 2 folders (Box 3)
- Campus Council, communications, 2002-2003 (Box 3)
- Campus Council nomination forms, 2002-2003 (Box 3)
- Newspaper articles for housing and Campus Council, 2002-2004 (Box 3)
- Campus Council, applications for program funding and budget, 2003-2004; 4 folders (Box 3)
- Campus Council, Finance Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 3)
- Leadership training for upperclass residential leaders, Autumn 2004 (Box 3)
- Quad meetings, 2004-2005 (Box 3)
- Residential governance leadership development manual, 2004-2005 (Box 3)
- Campus Council archive materials, 2005-2007 (Box 3)
- Web Archives, 2010-2010